<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lesson 2 - Layout AboutMe</string>
    <string name="name">Dinh Lam</string>
    <string name="yellow_star">Yellow star image</string>
    <string name="long_text">White-label apps can be a good outcome when you can sell a
        \ncertain concept to multiple companies, and only need to adjust some minor things before shipping for a new client.
        \nApart from that it can also come in handy when you have different versions of your app while the main functionality remains the same.
        \nA white-label project means you develop your main app once and make different flavours of that app for each version.
        \nThat way you can rapidly develop the app, move quickly when a new client comes in, and fix stuff fast when bugs appear.
        So what if we have this amazing idea, and it applies to multiple companies?
        \nOr what if we need different versions of an app, but they share most of the core functionality?
        \nWe can simply create our project as we normally do, but can take some stuff into account straight from the beginning.
        \nAlready have a solid app and want to white-label that? No worries, the same stuff applies to you!
        <![CDATA[You might’ve used them before: product flavours in your Gradle file.
    \nThey’re good for setting up multiple environments for example:
    \nstaging, production, etc. They’re super handy for setting up multiple flavours as well!
    \nLet’s have a short look into how the setup will look like. We can create our app like we normally would.
    \nAll the core functionality will go into the main part of our app.
    \nWhen we run a build, this is what’s going to be used in every case, regardless of the flavour.
    \nEverything that we specifically define for a flavour will then be used and will even override
    something when it’s also defined in our main part.
    \nThis can mean variables in our Gradle file, resources like app icons & colors or even layouts and classes!]]>
    </string>
    <string name="what_is_your_nickname">What is your nickname?</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
</resources>
